torquepowered.com 2018-06-20

# Privacy Policy | GarageGames.com

You must be logged in to post 

### GarageGames Privacy Statement

Last Updated: August 8, 2011

GarageGames.com is an Internet service (the "Service") operated by GarageGames LLC. ("GarageGames," "we," or "us").

At GarageGames, we respect the privacy of our users and the importance of the information they entrust to us. We summarize below the basic information policies and practices in place. To read the entire Privacy Policy of GarageGames, please _click here_. 

### Information we may collect _Read More_

We may collect information that can identify you ("personal information"), such as your name and email address, (i) when you (or other users) provide it to us when using the Service or in some other manner, or (ii) from our affiliates, business partners, and from other third parties. We may combine the personal information that we receive from different sources. 

We also may collect other types of information in the following ways when you access the Service:

  * Our server logs automatically collect information, such as your IP address, your browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit, which helps us track users’ movements through the games and other activities available through the Service and understand trends. 

  * We may assign your computer one or more cookies which may collect information to facilitate access to our Service and to personalize your online experience. 

  * We may use standard Internet tools, such web beacons, which collect information that tracks your use of our Service and enables us to customize our services and advertisements. 

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Should we ever become aware that we have collected such information, we will comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").

### Information others may collect _Read More_

We may allow third-parties to display advertisements and/or collect demographic research information through our Service.

  * We do not provide any personal information to these companies. 

  * These companies may use tracking tools, such as cookies, to collect information about computers used to view or interact with any advertisements. 

  * Some of these companies may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers consumers the ability to opt out of ad targeting by all member companies. 

If you post information about yourself or others, or communicate with others using our Service, please note that we cannot control who reads your postings or what they do with the information you provide. We encourage you to use caution in posting personal information.

### How we may use information we collect _Read More_

We may use information to:

  * Fulfill your requests for products and services; 

  * Customize the advertising and content that you see on our website; 

  * Facilitate use of the Service; 

  * Manage your account and your preferences; 

  * Analyze use of and improve the Service, products, services and activities offered through the Service; 

  * Identify and protect against fraudulent transactions and other misuses of Service; and 

  * Enforce our Terms of Service. 

### With whom we may share information we collect _Read More_

We will not share your personal information with others except as indicated below, or except when we inform you in advance and give you the opportunity to opt out. We may share personal information with:

  * Service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf; 

  * Other third parties in limited circumstances, such as complying with legal requirements, preventing fraud, and protecting the safety of our users. 

We may share aggregated, non-personal information in any of the above situations and also with affiliates, business partners, advertisers, demographic researchers and others.

### Your choices _Read More_

You may choose:

  * Not to provide personal information, although that may result in your inability to access the Service or use certain features of the Service; 

  * To stop receiving promotional emails or newsletters from us by sending an email, which includes your username and the email address linked to your account, to _[legal@GarageGames.com](mailto:legal@GarageGames.com)_ ; 

  * To review and update your personal information by contacting us at the email address below or, if you have an account with the Service, by logging into that account. 

### Security _Read More_

We take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure. However, we do not guaranty the safety of your personal information.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy _Read More_

We may occasionally update our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. If we make material changes in the way we collect, use, or share your personal information, we will notify you by posting notice of the changes through the Service.

### How to contact us

If you have any questions about this summary, or our information practices, please contact us by email or postal mail below:

GarageGames, LLC  
7674 West Lake Mead Blvd, Suite 210  
Las Vegas, Nevada 89128  
Attention: Privacy Officer  
Email: [legal@GarageGames.com](mailto:legal@GarageGames.com)
